careermitra.com 2019-04-08

# Privacy Policy - Career Mitra

Career Mitra Information Services Pvt. Ltd. (here after referred as ‘We’ or ‘Us’ or ‘Our’) is committed to ensure that your privacy is protected. Should We ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using careermitra.com (hereafter referred as website), then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes.

**What we collect?**

Registration is not mandatory to browse the website as a visitor, however to list an Educational Institution and perform certain functions such as writing a review etc, registration is compulsory. We collect the following information from you at the time of registration ‘ Your Name’, ‘Your Email’, ‘Phone’, ‘City’ and other personal information. We require this information for our internal records and book keeping, however you can access most parts of the website without revealing any information about you.

**Cookies & Tracking**

A Cookie is a small piece of data sent from a website and stored in a user’s web browser while the user is browsing that website. Every time the user loads the website, the browser sends the cookie back to the server to notify the website of the user’s previous activity (Source: Wikipedia).

We use cookies to collect information about your visits to www.careermitra.com. By default your browser accepts cookies to be placed on your machine however it is possible for you to disable the cookies by changing your browser settings.

We use Tracking technologies which will help us track your visits to our website, we may track your web browser, last visited web page before landing on our website, duration of your visit on our website and the navigation flow etc. We generate these reports and utilize it for improving our website and sections mostly accessed by the visitors.

**Confidentiality of your information**

Any information you share with us, example your Name, Email id, Mobile No. and Address of your house or office will not be disclosed to any third parties. However in circumstances when we believe (or notified by other users) that your activities are suspicious and require an investigation by law, we may share your personal information to appropriate authorities to help with their investigation.

**Questions related to our Privacy Policy**

If you have questions or concerns related to your privacy or should you feel it is necessary to contact us related to the Privacy Policy, you may contact us using the contact modes mentioned on our website. We respond and act promptly to address any grievance or concerns you may have.
